Davi Nomoeh Dani

 ♥ Central Java, ID □(62) 823-2544-1718 @dapi@duck.com
 □ linkedin.com/in/daphino
 ⊕ mr687.github.io

I'm a **Software Engineer** who is passionate about learning new things. 4 years of experience in developing and contributing to several projects, especially in **backend development**. Looking for a new job as my next career journey to sharpen up my technology knowledge & experiences in the Technology Industry.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Pesan.io Semarang, ID

Backend Engineer

Sep 2022 - Now

- Maintaining NodeJS Apps and deploying them to AWS servers to ensure high performance and reliability
- Reduce deployment time by up to 80% by optimizing compiler configurations
- Building a Business Intelligence app that quickly imports external data resources to our system, allowing for seamless integration with our clients
- Developing a module that integrates our system with external loyalty providers, enabling our clients to offer rewards and incentives to their customers
- Building Whatsapp Chatbot to Provide easy solutions to users who want to book a hotel room via chat
- Skills: Nest.js (Typescript), AWS, DevOps, Bash, Process Improvement, Container, CI/CD

PT TRAVELOKA INDONESIA

Tangerang, ID

Backend Engineer Intern (Cloud)

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

- Migrating current stack of application infrastructure to a serverless platform using AWS ECS Fargate & AWS Codepipeline
- Provisioning AWS Infrastructure using Terraform
- Provide understanding to stakeholders about a new container stack deployment
- Collaborate with many teams that require more collaboration and communication
- Minimize the same actions with creating a bot using Node.Js with research
- Skills: Working proficiency in English, Java Springboot, AWS, DevOps, Bash, Terraform, Datadog, Process Improvement, Container, CI/CD

SRW&CO. Jakarta, ID

Fullstack Engineer

Fullstack Engineer

Oct 2021 - Feb 2022

- **Project**: Profesi.io (The Future of Al-driven People Management)
- Develop RESTful API using Adonis.js framework and database PostgreSQL
- Handles heavy computing for user-recommended content based on user's personalization by creating a scheduler
- Refactor Admin Dashboard UI as per Figma with frontend framework Nuxt.js
- Integrate AgGrid library and Quill Editor by creating custom modules to suit development needs
- Skills: Adonis.js, Nuxt.js, Typescript, Redis, PostgreSQL, Vue.js

PT DIGITAL AGENCY NUSANTARA

Bandung, ID

Jan 2021 - Mar 2021

• **Project:** EPT.co.id (English Proficiency Test Platform)

- Develop website using Laravel 8.x and Livewire
- Payment gateway integration (Midtrans)
- Integrate Whatsapp API (WooWa)
- Integrate Whatsapp Arr (Woowa)
 Integrate Shipping services (RajaOngkir)
- Challenges: Create a real-time and fast exam system
- **Skills**: Backend framework **Laravel**, Frontend framework **Livewire**, **Turbolink.js**, Css framework **Bootstrap**, **MySQL**, **Ubuntu Server**

SEMANGAT.IN (Donation Platform)

Remote

Fullstack Engineer Nov 2020- Jan 2021

- Develop website using Laravel 8.x using Repository Pattern for more structural code
- Payment gateway integration (Xendit & Midtrans)
- Skills: Laravel, MySQL, Payment Gateway, Css framework Bootstrap

KODINGWORKS Semarang, ID Backend Engineer Jul 2020- Nov 2020

- **Project:** Waste for Change (W4C)
- Develop RESTful API using Laravel & Laravel Passport for authentication token

- Collaborate with frontend team & android team
- Payment gateway integration (Xendit & Midtrans)
- Executing queue jobs with cron-job system on schedule

DIAN NUSWANTORO UNIVERSITY

Semarang, ID

Fullstack Engineer Intern

Dec 2019 - Mar 2020

- **Project**: Academic system for the Faculty of Informatics
- Develop legalized demand system with delivery feature (Integrated with Delivery service)
- Develop a broadcasting system for email notification to lectures
- Remote web server configuration with SSH

ALAGRAPH.COM (Media Platform)

Makassar, ID

Frontend Developer

Jul 2017 - Dec 2017

- Responsible for frontend web development using Codeigniter and CSS Bootstrap
- Improve creative skills to create new designs for the news web portal (UI & UX requirements)

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Vooka - Interactive Music Bot for Discord

- Stack: Built with Node.js (Typescript) & Discord.js; Store client data to the Database (PostgreSQL)
- **Challenges**: Handle search based on queries with autocomplete and return related playlist; Handles even-loop while the bot is used by multiple users.
- View more on: https://github.com/vookav2

Voonime - Anime Released Reminder / Notification

- Build with Node.js
- Scrape list of anime videos and release schedules from other websites
- Create a scheduler to check & send the released info to the users
- More on: https://github.com/mr687/voonime

Finda - Anonymous Chatting for Whatsapp

- Build with Node.js
- Challenges: Meet 2 strangers in the same chat room based on the queue system
- More on: https://github.com/mr687/finda

EDUCATION

Dian Nuswantoro University (Udinus)

Semarang, ID

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering, Major in Computer Science

Dec 2019 - Dec 2023

• GPA: 3.77/4.0 (6th semester)

SMK Tunas Harapan Pati

Pati, ID

.

Computer & Network Engineering, Science

Jan 2016 - Oct 2019

• **Competitions**: Android-app innovation (Team); IT Software Application

AWARD & CERTIFICATION

Associate Data Scientist - LSP Udinus	Jul 2022
Backend Laravel Development - Hacktiv8	Mar 2022
 Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User - 	May 2020
Coursera	
 Android Developer (Java) - Dicoding Academy 	Dec 2019
 2nd Winner of IT Software Application - LKS Jawa Tengah 	Oct 2018
XXVII	
 Web Developer (PHP Codeigniter) - Trainit 	Oct 2017

OTHER

Languages: Conversational Proficiency in English, Fluent in Bahasa Indonesia (native)

Technical Skills: Python, Jupyter Notebook, Golang, MongoDB, Heroku, Google Cloud Platform (GCP)

[other skills from the job description]

Familiars: Blockchain, WEB 3 Technology